http://www.aupha.org/about/privacypolicy

Skip to main content (Press Enter).
Sign in
Skip auxiliary navigation (Press Enter).
JoinStoreContact UsCode of Conduct
Skip main navigation (Press Enter).
Toggle navigation
Content types
AnnouncementsBlogsCommunitiesDiscussionsEventsGlossarySite ContentLibraries
Date range
on this day
between these dates
Posted by
About Vision, Mission, Values, PhilosophyBoardStaffHistory of AUPHACorporate PartnersMarketing OpportunitiesPress RoomResourcesBylawsPrivacy PolicyMembership Members OnlyExplore AUPHABachelor's ProgramsMaster's ProgramsDoctoral ProgramsAffiliate MembershipInternational ProgramsIndividualsGet InvolvedUPDDuesAUPHA AwardsCertification Certification OverviewCertification DocumentsEvents 2021 Annual MeetingAcademic Program and Practitioner WorkshopWebinar SeriesEvent CalendarPublications Journal of Health Administration EducationAUPHA ExchangeHealth Administration PressFree Marketing AssistanceBody of KnowledgeResilience & Well-Being Tool KitCareers Careers in Health AdministrationFind a JobPost a JobFaculty Faculty Resources 2020 Annual Meeting RecordingsCOVID-19 Resources COVID-19 WebinarsFilerman PrizeThompson PrizeGlandon Family ScholarshipGraham PrizeStudents Find a Health Administration ProgramHAMPCASCurrent StudentsFuture StudentsHealth Professions Week 2020Complimentary
Webinars in Honor of 2020 GraduatesAUPHA Network My ProfileFind a MemberBrowse LibrariesOpen ForumMy Communities
Privacy Policy
We respect your privacy.
Any personal
information you provide to us including and similar to your name,
address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released,
sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of our organization except as noted below.
With whom do we share the personal information we collect through this site?
Our Service Providers
We
may share your personal information with companies (including our
affiliates) that perform services on our behalf, for example, companies
that help process credit card payments. Our service providers are
required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal
information we share with them and to use it only to provide specific
services on our behalf.
Business Transfers
Your
personal information may be transferred to another entity (either an
affiliated entity or an unrelated third party) in connection with a
merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar corporate event. If such
a transfer were ever to occur, the acquiring entity’s use of your
personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy.
Government and Legal Disclosures
We
may disclose the personal information we collect through this Site,
when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply
with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate
a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce our Terms and Conditions of Use, Code of Conduct or other agreements that govern your use of this Site;
or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our users,
or others.
External Sites
We are not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You
are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before
disclosing any personal information.
Cookies
A
"cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and
allows us to recognize you each time you visit this
site (personalization, etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal
information, and we do not use cookies to collect
personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content
providers such as newsfeeds.
Remember the risks whenever you use the internet.
While
we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot
guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy
of any passwords or other account information. In addition other
Internet sites or services that may be accessible through our site have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and
therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their
policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
For any other information please contact us using the Contact Us page.
Association of University Programs in Health Administration
AboutVision, Mission, Values, PhilosophyBoardStaffHistory of AUPHACorporate PartnersMarketing OpportunitiesPress RoomResourcesBylawsPrivacy PolicyMembershipMembers OnlyExplore AUPHABachelor's ProgramsMaster's ProgramsDoctoral ProgramsAffiliate MembershipInternational ProgramsIndividualsGet InvolvedUPDDuesAUPHA AwardsCertificationCertification OverviewCertification DocumentsEvents2021 Annual MeetingAcademic Program and Practitioner WorkshopWebinar SeriesEvent CalendarPublicationsJournal of Health Administration EducationAUPHA ExchangeHealth Administration PressFree Marketing AssistanceBody of KnowledgeResilience & Well-Being Tool KitCareersCareers in Health AdministrationFind a JobPost a JobFacultyFaculty ResourcesCOVID-19 ResourcesFilerman PrizeThompson PrizeGlandon Family ScholarshipGraham PrizeStudentsFind a Health Administration ProgramHAMPCASCurrent StudentsFuture StudentsHealth Professions Week 2020Complimentary
Webinars in Honor of 2020 GraduatesAUPHA NetworkMy ProfileFind a MemberBrowse LibrariesOpen ForumMy Communities
Phone:
202-763-7283
Email:
aupha@aupha.org
Copyright 2016 AUPHA. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy  Terms of Use
Powered by Higher Logic
